A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Vice Presidential, Series 6 FA459
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Vice Presidential, 6
  - Contact Sheets, 1973-1977; 1
    - G2054 - 2a-6a General Assembly of the International Press Institute in Philadelphia, Pa., 7a-9a Bob Mosbacher, 1976 May 11; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2055 - General Assembly of the International Press Institute in Philadelphia, Pa., 1976 May 11; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2056 - 4a-15a General Assembly of the International Press Institute in Philadelphia, Pa., 16a-21a Meeting with New Zealand Parlimentarians, 22a Bob Mosbacher, 1976 May 11; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2057 - Vice President visits disaster site in Italy, 1976 May 13; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2058 - Vice President visits disaster site in Italy, 1976 May 13; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2059 - Vice President visits disaster site in Italy, 1976 May 13; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2060 - Vice President visits disaster site in Italy, 1976 May 13; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2061 - Vice President visits disaster site in Italy, 1976 May 13; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2062 - G2064 - Frankfurt, Germany, 1976 May 14; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2065 - G2069 - Berlin, Germany, 1976 May 14; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2070 - Various pics aboard Air Force II with Arthur Brown, Dan Parker and Senator Mathias of Maryland, 1976 May 15; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2071 - G2077 - Frankfurt, Germany, 1976 May 15; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2078 - 2a-20a The Vice President briefs the President on Italy's earthquake, 21a-24a Guy Stever and Doug Bennett, 1976 May 17; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2079 - Vice President briefs the President on Italy's earthquake area, 1976 May 17; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2080 - Secretary Richardson, Richard Darman, Betsy Ancker-Johnson, Simon Ramo, Herbert Holloman, Marina Whitman, 1976 May 19; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2081 - Barber Conable taping; reception for French President Valery Giscard d'Estaing, 1976 May 19; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2082 - Barber Conable taping; reception for French President Valery Giscard d'Estaing, 1976 May 19; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2083 - Jack Germond; Time Magazine; Italian relief committee announcement, 1976 May 19; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2084 - Japanese Diet members; Italian relief committee announcement, 1976 May 19; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2085 - Yorktown, Virginia, 1976 May 19; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2086 - Yorktown, Virginia; Simcha Dinitz and Golda Meir, 1976 May 19; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2087 - Yorktown, Virginia, 1976 May 19; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2088 - Vice Presidential service badge award, 1976 May 20; Color (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2089 - Rogers Morton; PFC reception, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1976 May 20; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2090 - PFC reception, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1976 May 20; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2091 - Al Haig and Capt. John Howe; meeting on chart books; PFC reception, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1976 May 20; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2092 - G2095 - Touro Synagogue, Newport, Rhode Island, 1976 May 23; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2096 - G2099 - Albany, New York, 1976 May 24; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 26, Volume 13)
    - G2100 - State gifts, 1976 May 24; Color (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2101 - Mr. and Mrs. William Whyte private dinner, 1976 May 25; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2102 - Mr. and Mrs. William Whyte private dinner, 1976 May 25; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2103 - Jesse Jackson, Veneman and group; Hans Mark and James Fletcher; Mr. and Mrs. William Whyte private dinner, 1976 May 25; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2104 - Jesse Jackson, Veneman and group; Polish international delegation; Hans Mark and James Fletcher; Mr. and Mrs. William Whyte private dinner, 1976 May 25; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2105 - National Conference On Regulatory Reform; Egyptian youth leaders; Marino de Medici II, 1976 May 26; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2106 - National Conference On Regulatory Reform; Greater San Francisco Chamber of Commerce; Egyptian youth leaders, 1976 May 26; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2107 - Japanese Ambassador Fumihiko Togo; Lt. Gen. Vernon Walters, 1977 May 27; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2108 - International Standards Organization, 1976 May 27; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2109 - G2112 - Air Force Academy commencement, Colorado, 1976 June 3; Color (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2113 - Governors and mayors revenue sharing meeting, 1976 June 3; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2114 - Governors and mayors revenue sharing meeting; King Juan Carlos, Blair House, 1976 June 3; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2115 - Governors and mayors revenue sharing meeting; King Juan Carlos, Blair House, 1976 June 3; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2116 - Staff meeting; George Kuper, Executive Director, Productivity Commission, swearing-in, 1976 June 4; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2117 - Edward Teller; staff meeting; George Kuper; Executive Director, Productivity Commission, swearing-in, 1976 June 4; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2118 - Rep. Moorhead; Zarb; Diane Bailey; Shirley Brown's birthday; PFC reception, 1976 June 8; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2119 - Diane Bailey; Sen. Randolph (WV); Rep. Diggs (MI; PFC reception; Australian ballet, 1976 June 8; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2120 - Australian Ballet, Kennedy Center, 1976 June 8; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2121 - National Broadcast Editorial Association, 1976 June 9; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2122 - Mrs. Rockefeller's birthday, USS Sequoia, hosted by President and Mrs. Ford, 1976 June 9; Color (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2123 - Mrs. Rockefeller's birthday, USS Sequoia, hosted by President and Mrs. Ford, 1976 June 9; Color (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2124 - Inter-American Defense College, Fort McNair; Canadian Ambassador Jack Warren and First Secretary Lorne Clark, 1976 June 10; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2125 - Inter-American Defense College, Fort McNair; Marquis Childs; Jim Henderson; Canadian Ambassador Jack Warren and First Secretary Lorne Clark; Sen. Giorgio Oliva and Ambassador Gaja (2 sheets), 1976 June 10; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2126 - Robert Hartmann; Linwood Holton; British Ambassador Ramsbotham; Eric Sevareid; old Senate chamber rededication, 1976 June 16; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2127 - Old Senate chamber rededication; Robert Monks; National Housing Conference dinner, 1976 June 16; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2128 - Old Senate chamber rededication, 1976 June 16; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2129 - G2133 - New York Republican State Committee dinner, 1976 June 17; Color (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2134 - National Housing Conference dinner; National Emergency Command, 1976 June 17; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2135 - National Housing Conference dinner; Robert Georgine dinner, 1976 June 17; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2136 - National Emergency Command, 1976 June 17; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2137 - New York Republican State Committee dinner, New York, New York; National Emergency Command, 1976 June 17; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2138 - G2141 - Greensboro, North Carolina, 1976 June 18; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2142 - G2144 - New Jersey Republican State Committee dinner, West Orange, New Jersey, 1976 June 21; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2145 - Joint service for Ambassador Meloy and Mr. Waring; New Jersey Republican State Committee dinner, 1976 June 21; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2146 - American Friends of Hebrew University; CIA headquarters, Langley, Virginia, 1976 June 22; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2147 - CIA headquarters, Langley, Virginia, 1976 June 22; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2148 - American Friends of Hebrew University; CIA headquarters, Langley, Virginia, 1976 June 22; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2149 - Israeli Ambassador Simcha Dinitz, 1976 June 23; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2150 - New York Republican delegation; Tom Braden; Dutch TV interview, 1976 June 23; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 27, Volume 14)
    - G2151 - Congressional Leadership meeting; Bicentennial gift, 1976 June 24; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2152 - Congressional Leadership meeting; Bicentennial gift, 1976 June 24; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2153 - Nassau County Republican Committee dinner, 1976 June 24; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2154 - Marshall Green, Louis Hellman; Donna Blume; Pearl Bailey; aboard Air Force 2, 1976 June 24; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2155 - Mr. and Mrs. John Pell; Megan Marshack; aboard Air Force 2, 1976 June 24; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2156 - Nassau County Republican Committee dinner, 1976 June 24; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2157 - Sen. Tower (TX); Cliff Evans; Tunisian mosaic exhibit opening, 1976 June 29; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2158 - Sen. Beall (MD) reception; reception for Japanese Prime Minister Miki, 1976 June 29; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2159 - Berlin legislators; Cliff Evans; Tunisian mosaic exhibit opening, 1976 June 29; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2160 - Sen. Beall (MD) reception; reception for Japanese Prime Minister Miki, 1976 June 29; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2161 - Estes Kefauver Union of the Free award luncheon; Veneman, Art Quern, Grady Means, 1976 July 1; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2162 - Australian legislators; Estes Kefauver Union of the Free award luncheon, 1976 July 1; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2163 - G2165 - National Air and Space Museum, 1976 July 1; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2166 - Dinner at the Italian Embassy, 1976 July 1; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2167 - UNIVAC I 25th anniversary and the release of Status; dinner at the Italian Embassy, 1976 July 1; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2168 - UNIVAC I 25th anniversary and the release of Status, 1976 July 1; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2169 - John Warner, Joseph Danzansky, Bicentennial medallion; Donna Blume; Reception at the Marine Commandant's residence, 1976 July 2; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2170 - John Warner, Joseph Danzansky, Bicentennial medallion; reception at the Norwegian Embassy, 1976 July 2; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2171 - Reception at the Norwegian Embassy; reception at the Marine Commandant's residence; National Archives, 1976 July 2; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2172 - National Archives; reception at the Marine Commandant's residence, 1976 July 2; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2173 - National Archives; reception at the Marine Commandant's residence, 1976 July 2; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2174 - G2179 - The American Bicentennial grand parade, 1976 July 3; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2180 - G2187 - Operation Sail '76, Bicentennial program, 1976 July 4; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2188 - G2189 - Happy Birthday USA program, Washington Monument Grounds, 1976 July 4; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2190 - Executive committee of the National Center for Productivity and Quality of Working Life, 1976 July 7; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2191 - Henry Catto; Executive committee of the National Center for Productivity and Quality of Working Life, 1976 July 7; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2192 - Queen Elizabeth II; Queen Elizabeth II at the Smithsonian Institution, 1976 July 8; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2193 - Congressional luncheon for Queen Elizabeth II; Queen Elizabeth II at the Smithsonian Institution, 1976 July 8; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2194 - Congressional luncheon for Queen Elizabeth II, 1976 July 8; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2195 - Queen Elizabeth II at the Smithsonian Institution, 1976 July 8; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2196 - Rockefeller Washington Monument address; Congressional luncheon for Queen Elizabeth II, 1976 July 8; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2197 - Kathy Huldrum, Huldrum and Howard Dixon; Quern, Cannon, Howe, Herter, Humphries, and Veneman; James Needham; Kenzo Kono, President of the Japanese House of Councilors, 1976 July 8; Black and White (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2198 - Queen Elizabeth II departure; luncheon for Prince Abdallah of Saudi Arabia, 1976 July 8; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2199 - Queen Elizabeth II departure, 1976 July 8; Color (Box 7, Folder 28, Volume 14)
    - G2200 - Luncheon for Prince Abdallah of Saudi Arabia, 1976 July 8; Color (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2201 - Daniel Boorstin; Brazilian Ambassador Pinheiro, 1976 July 13; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2202 - Morrow, Wallison, Howe, Shafer, Allison and Veneman; White House switchboard operators; Nancy Kissinger, 1976 July 14; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2203 - Morrow, Wallison, Howe, Shafer, Allison and Veneman; White House switchboard operators, 1976 July 14; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2204 - State gifts, 1976 July 15; Color (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2205 - Bill Tammeus, Kansas City Star" ", 1976 July 16; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2206 - Bill Tammeus, Kansas City Star" ", 1976 July 16; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2207 - G2209 - Delaware state Republican fundraising dinner, Wilmington, Delaware, 1976 July 17; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2210 - G2211 - VP in limousine; Sen. Humphrey (MN); Melvin Laird; Hans Mark and daughter; Gov. Rhodes (OH), 1976 July 20; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2212 - Gov. Longley (ME) and Ray Shafer; Philip Crowe; Andy and John Schnatz; Jesse Jackson, H. Hartford Brookings, and Veneman, 1976 July 21; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2213 - Andy and John Schnatz; Jesse Jackson, H. Hartford Brookings, and Veneman, 1976 July 21; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2214 - Ambassador Von Staden of Germany and Members of Muhlenberg Memorial, 1976 July 22; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2216 - I.W. Abel, productivity subcommittee; Shirley Temple Black; Malcolm Fraser, Australian Prime Minister, 1976 July 28; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2217 - John McCone; Bob Ajamian; Malcolm Fraser, Australian Prime Minister, 1976 July 18; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2217a - West German Ambassador Von Staden; Ambassador Kenneth Rush, 1976 July 22; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2218 - Reception for Prime Minister Fraser, 1976 July 28; Color (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2219 - Republican National Hispanic Assembly, 1976 July 29; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2220 - Republican National Hispanic Assembly, 1976 July 29; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2221 - Reception for Northeast Republican State Chairmen and Maine Republican State Committee, Seal Harbor, Maine, 1976 August 2; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2222 - Reception for Northeast Republican State Chairmen and Maine Republican State Committee, Seal Harbor, Maine, 1976 August 2; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2223 - Reception for Northeast Republican State Chairmen and Maine Republican State Committee, Seal Harbor, Maine, 1976 August 2; Color (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2224 - Theodore White; GRF with VP staff, 1976 August 3; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2225 - GRF with VP staff, Oval Office, 1976 August 3; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2226 - Copy of statue bust?, 1976 August 3; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2227 - Dinner with Finnish President Kekkonen, 1976 August 4; Color (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2228 - Dinner with Finnish President Kekkonen, 1976 August 4; Color (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2229 - NAR in EOB office, 1976 August 5; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2230 - Lou Cannon and Ed Walsh; Kathy Huldrum; Defense briefing, 1976 August 5; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2231 - Secretary Richardson; Advisory Council on Historic Preservation; luncheon for Finnish President Urho Kekkonen, 1976 August 5; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2232 - Secretary Richardson; Advisory Council on Historic Preservation; luncheon for Finnish President Urho Kekkonen, 1976 August 5; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2233 - PFC headquarters, 1976 August 10; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2234 - PFC headquarters, 1976 August 10; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2235 - Professor and Mrs. Irwin Gellman; Teddy Gleason and Bob Armao, 1976 August 11; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2236 - Columbian Ambassador Turbay-Ayalla, 1976 August 11; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2237 - Singapore Ambassador Monteiro, 1976 August 12; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2238 - Singapore Ambassador Monteiro; Arthur Fletcher, 1976 August 12; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2239 - G2245 - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 August 15; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2246 - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 August 16; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2247 - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 August 16; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2248 - G2252 - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 August 16; Color (Box 8, Folder 29, Volume 15)
    - G2253 - G2258 - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 August 17; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2259 - G2262 - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 August 18; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2263 - G2268 - Republican National Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 1976 August 19; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2269 - Kansas City departure; aboard Air Force II; Jackson Hole, Wyoming, 1976 August 20; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2270 - Jackson Hole, Wyoming, 1976 August 20; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2271 - Kansas City departure, 1976 August 20; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2272 - G2281 - Seal Harbor, Maine, 1976 September 7; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2282 - VP and Mrs. Rockefeller and Mrs. Leone at a performance of Macbeth, Kennedy Center, 1976 September 7; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2283 - G2287 - VP staff party, Air and Space Museum, 1976 September 9; Color (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2288 - Inaugural medal royalties presentation; Ambassador Hodgson, 1976 September 8; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2289 - Inaugural medal royalties presentation, 1976 September 8; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2290 - Etienne Dailly; Dr. Currie; Ambassador Zahedi (Iran); Ambassador Sensi and Mr. Dechiara, 1976 September 15; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2291 - Quincy Rogers and Bill Hermelin, Privacy Commission; Etienne Dailly; Jim McCarthy; Secretary Richardson and John Kendrick, 1976 September 15; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2292 - Moose Roast, Foxhall Road, 1976 September 15; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2293 - Moose Roast, Foxhall Road; Sen. and Mrs. Dole (KS), 1976 September 15; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2294 - G2299 - Sen. Dole (KS); Buffalo, Rochester, Syracuse, Binghamton, and New York, New York, 1976 September 16; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 30, Volume 15)
    - G2300 - G2302 - Sen. Dole (KS); Buffalo, Rochester, Syracuse, Binghamton, and New York, New York, 1976 September 16; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2303 - G2304 - Governors Club reception, Pocantico Hills, 1976 September 17; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2305 - G2310 - Secret Service reception, Pocantico Hills, 1976 September 18; Color (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2311 - NAR in Binghamton, New York (copy), 1976 September 21; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2312 - Jimmy Lile presentation; Tom Aranda, 1976 September 20; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2313 - Intelligence community staff representatives, 1976 September 20; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2314 - G2316 - Chicago, Illinois, 1976 September 21; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2317 - G2323 - Cleveland, Columbus and Cincinnati, Ohio, 1976 September 22; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2324 - President Tolbert, Liberia, at Blair House, 1976 September 23; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2325 - J. Mulliken and J. Osborn; Domestic Council staff; Greek parliamentarians; President Tolbert, Liberia, 1976 September 23; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2326 - G2330 - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1976 September 28; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2331 - G2335 - Hasbrook Heights and Dover, New Jersey; Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1976 September 28; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2336 - Air Force Two crew, 1976 September 29; Color (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2337 - G2339 - Erie, Pennsylvania, 1976 September 29; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2340 - Ambassador Touminer; Dr. and Mrs. Franklin Murphy, 1976 September 30; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2341 - G2345 - 2000 Years Of North American Indian Art exhibition, London, England, 1976 October 6; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2346 - Salute to the President dinner, Chicago, Illinois, 1976 October 7; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)
    - G2347 - Salute to the President dinner, Chicago, Illinois, 1976 October 7; Black and White (Box 8, Folder 31, Volume 16)